メルエムに対し
Alone? I'm impressed.
時間稼ぎのために 勝負を挑んだプフは
Where do you want to die?
まだ　催眠状態にない人民達に
I'll humor any requests.
鱗粉を散布していた 急がねば　メルエム様が あれのことを思い出す前に…
I'd prefer a deserted wasteland,
with no one nearby. Since I'll have you screaming
at the top of your lungs.
一刻も早く 娘を抹殺しに向かいたいのに 何としても！ 今回が正真正銘　最後の機会！
Condition x And x Condition
パームは　ここに残ってる 女性４人を連れて来てくれ。
A small clan, with Scarlet Eyes,
that lived in the Lukso Province.
あの４人　逃げてないの？
Five years ago, you attacked us.
ああ　ガムテープで 目と手を縛ったほうがいい。
Scarlet Eyes? What's that? The name of a treasure?
俺を見られたら説明とか長くなる。
Sorry, doesn't ring a bell...
そうね　分かったわ。 ところで　何で あいつら乗せて来たの？
But five years ago,
I was definitely a member. When you kill a completely
innocent bystander, what are you people thinking?
地下倉庫の奥に　娘が 捕らわれているってことだけ
Nothing at all.
王か護衛軍に伝えてくれればいい。
Scum!
俺達が交渉したいって 言ってるってな。 その後は自由だ。
You will atone through death!
どうせ罠があんだろ？ それは王に言うぜ。 言わなきゃ不自然だし 俺が疑われる。
Fools like you are the reason
I never get sick of killing.
ああ。 いや それ以前　敵のパシリ自体
Wanna know what I enjoy most?
王の逆鱗に触れかねねえ！ 誰がやるかよ　そんなこと
Denying those who come
in search of revenge!
プフを抹消してでも 見ておいたほうが…
Those chains are dangerous.
パーム。 大丈夫
I don't know what kind
of trick he used on them, but they hold an abnormal amount of Nen.
ウェルフィン これが終わったら自由なんだ。
Strike first to win!
ジャイロに会いに行けよ。 えっ！
Got him.
気安く　あいつの名前 呼ぶんじゃ　ねえ！
That's a surprise...
てめぇに何が分かる　あぁ!?
After taking that punch,
he still has the strength to attack?
分かるよ　ザイカハル。 あっ。
But his left arm is useless now.
何で…。 何で　俺の…。 前の…。
Unscathed? Impossible... Considering the amount
of Nen in those chains, he must be a Manipulator or a Conjurer...
誰にも言ってないはず
I would guess the former.
俺は多分　もう 昔の名前　思い出せないけど
But only an Enhancer should be
able to block my attack.
仲間さ。
What is he?
仲間？ 前のな。
Was that punch
俺達　ＮＧＬの。
That wasn't even funny.
違うか？
Don't worry. That was twenty percent of my strength.
うっ　うぅ…。
This time, I'll use half!
ブロヴーダも　前世を 忘れているだけで　仲間のはず。
Here!
イカルゴ　何で てめぇは知ってんだよ？
Damn!
ジャイロが 生きてんのを知らなきゃ
Here!
そんな言い方しねえだろ！ ああ　確かに。
Damn, he keeps darting around. But...
でも　知ってるんじゃなくて そうとしか思えないからだよ。 ん？
I'll regret not using that
chance to chain you up?
あいつが ただ　消化されるわけないだろ。
Stop making excuses,
and give me your best shot. You're wasting my time.
チクショウ　チクショウ
A smoke screen? His presence has disappeared.
チクショウ！
He's using In!
１０分過ぎても　ピトーが 戻る気配なんて　全くねえぞ
No one can withstand a full-strength Big Bang Impact.
降りろ。
I didn't think you knew how to use In.
外に出れば 状況は　ひと目で分かるはずだ。
was intended to conceal both your
physical body and your presence. However... I, too, can use In.
むかつくが イカルゴの言う通りだよ
These chains were fortified
with a Conjurer's Nen. Meaning I can use In to
render them invisible.
ジャイロが殺されて 終わるわけがねえ
So you kept the chains out to trick us into thinking they were real?
なら　奴らは敵
Precisely.
目を覚まさせてくれた礼だ メッセンジャーくらい やってやるよ！
I pretended to be a Manipulator
using Nen-controlled chains, so my enemies would only be
alert to the visible chains.
ん？
While you were making empty threats, my chains were already
wrapped around your body.
止まれ！
You've been captured.
ユピー殿？
Damn... But how? He has an Enhancer's defensive power...
早速　護衛軍のお出ましか
And the Nen in his conjured
chains is incredibly strong...
ユピー殿　至急
That's impossible.
王に　お伝えせねば ならないことがございます。
A Nen user can only fully master
their innate category.
地下倉庫に？ はっ。
Let me illuminate you, before
sending you to the other side.
はい　一刻も早く 王様へお伝えください。
Those eyes...
なるほど　勝負なんだから
There were a bunch of them,
in the middle of nowhere.
王に伝えなくとも問題なしだ
The boss really liked those eyes.
プフの奴
They were pretty strong!
ここまで考えての提案だとしたら 大したもんだ
Then, you're a survivor?
はっ。 取りあえず プフが戻ったら知らせねえと
Let's see which is stronger, your grudge or my power!
それにしても　ピトーは 一体　何してやがるんだ？
Is that all you can think about? You'll never be able to break these chains!
ユピー殿！ あ？
When my eyes turn scarlet,
I become a Specialist. What was that?
お聞きしたいことが。 何だ？ 前世の記憶はありますか？
When I am a Specialist, I wield full control over
every category of Nen.
キメラに　なる前の。
And this is my power...
あ？　ねえよ　そんなもん。
Absolute Mastery
Emperor Time Emperor Time!
ユピー殿。 おい！　いいかげんに…。
Yes, when I heard about conjuring, that was the first thing that came to mind.
うわっ。
Chains, huh...
ん？
Because there's evil running
loose that needs to be
俺を攻撃すれば　反撃する。
chained down to hell.
いくつか質問する。
Really, now?
５秒以内に答えろ。 グゥ…。
I get the feeling that you're
actually just chaining yourself. What would you know?
調子　乗ってんじゃねえぞ！
Hey! Wait up! I'm your teacher!
クソが！
I'm not finished talking! Hold it right there...
勝負…
Man, you're so stubborn.
足りぬ　何かが…
Really?! Yeah, you only hear what you want to hear.
そうだ
Come up with a rule for your chains. One that you are prepared to follow.
余は　誰かと戦っていた そして余は
It's a double-edged sword. If you break the rule you set,
you could lose your Nen.
まだ　勝っていない
My objective is to find my brethren's Scarlet Eyes
その者に　一度も
and to capture the spiders. I want chains that are
うっ。
unbreakable by the spiders,
the Phantom Troupe. The spiders will be my only targets.
クッ 予想以上に時間がかかった
I'll stake my life on it!
もう　とっくに ピトーは戻っているはず
Hey, Kurapika...
王が　焦れてなければいいが
When your eyes are scarlet,
your aura spikes.
ユピーは？
Let's try water divination again!
ユピーは　どこです？ ん？
A Specialist?
あれは…。 あっ。
You have full control over
every other category?
ユピー？
Holy Chain: Healing Thumb
そ…　そんな…。
I can use enhanced self-healing to completely recover a broken arm.
もう　大丈夫。 どういう意味だ？　パーム。
While you fought the Mafia
and the Shadow Beasts, the other spiders stayed out of it altogether.
王！　メルエム様！ ユピーが殺されました。
That told me you preferred to fight alone, and that they trusted that
your strength would prevail.
敵にも　かなりの手だれが まだ　います！
I prefer to fight one-on-one.
ピトーは？ はっ…。
That made you a perfect target.
いえ　まだ。 ならば　ようやく 余も始動できるわけだな。
An Enhancer who was confident
in his offense and defense.
い…　いえ　メルエム様！
You met every condition I
required for my first target.
状況が変わりました！ やめると申すか？
Because then I could test if my Chain Jail
うっ。
would be effective on the rest of the Troupe.
ならば余の勝利。 洗いざらい話してもらうぞ。
Chain Jail forcefully activates Zetsu
upon any Troupe member it ensnares.
うっ！ それでいいのか？
It also paralyzes them.
「もう　大丈夫」って どういう意味だ？　パーム。
So that's why I can't muster any aura...
キルアの結論は 王にとって彼女は特別。
Zetsu nullifies aura.
でも　護衛軍では 意見が分かれている。
Meaning you'd need to use
なぜなら
physical strength alone to break these chains. Damn!
ピトーは　そのコを救い　守り プフは殺そうとした。
If the Troupe member with the most
physical strength cannot break the chains, the others will certainly be
unable to escape Chain Jail.
つまり　彼女は
His forced activation of Zetsu here is bad...
王にとって　もろ刃の剣。
Aura is the basis of all Nen.
いやいや… 俺には信じられねえ。 王の意思に逆らって 護衛軍の統率が乱れるなんて
If it's sealed off, you can't use your power.
あり得ねえよ！
A technique for sealing Nen...
そう？ でも　なら　何で 私や　あなたは　ここにいるの？
This guy thought everything through.
普通のキメラなら「あり得ない」が いろいろ起こっている。
It looks as though my enhanced fist
絶対と言い切れる根拠はある？
is slightly stronger than your physical brawn.
うん。
That's valuable information.
ごめんね でも　私が言いたいのは 王への忠誠と　護衛軍の分裂は
Then I can beat every Troupe member
barehanded, provided I've chained them.
必ずしも矛盾しないってこと。 王が大事にしている人間がいる。
Tell me everything you know.
「だから　その人を守る」と 「だから　その人を殺す」は
Where are the other spiders?
どちらも成り立つのよ。
Kill me.
それと　「もう　大丈夫」は どう　つながるんだよ？
What abilities do they have?
王の最初の「円」から およそ２０分経過。
Kill me.
最初の「円」の時 私は　このコを背負ってた。
It makes me sick...
王が そのことに気付いていたなら
The sensation left on my hand.
まず　私の元に来たはず。
The grating sound of each strike.
そうしなかったのは 髪の毛で覆っていたから。
The smell of blood! It all throws my senses into disarray...
背負っていたものを　人と 認識できなかったと考えられる。 そこまではいい？ うん。
How can you do these things,
yet feel and think nothing at all?! Answer me!
論理的だし異論ねえよ 話は全く見えないけどな。
Kill me.
それって　ナックルとメレオロン 見殺しにして
This is your last chance.
交渉しねえってことかよ？
I just placed a conditional
bond on your heart.
まさか… 交渉は　もちろんするわよ。 ただし　できる限りの時間を稼ぐの そのためにも
If you break the rule I set, the bond will activate, crushing your heart.
このコは　王に見つからない場所に かくまう必要があるわ。
The rule is that you must answer my question honestly.
王が　死ぬまで。
Abide by that rule, and I shall
allow you to live a bit longer. Where are the other spiders?!
何で 「もう　大丈夫」になるんだよ？ もっと　はっきり教えてくれ！
I spent too much time in that state...
数時間のうちに
Why didn't you call? Are you okay? Yeah.
王は死ぬ。
I'm glad to hear that... What about on your side?
もっと奥がいいわ。
I see. I understand.
私達は残酷よ。
A chain user...
いえ　それ以上に…。
But in a one-on-one fight, he is most
vulnerable to those two categories. Many Conjurers give special powers
ピトー　ピトー！ 一体どこです？
If he fails to return by dawn, there will be a change in plans.
ピトー!! うっ！
Shalnark senses the danger,
as Uvogin fails to return.
あっ！
Their leader, Chrollo, prepares to terminate the chain user.